
<string_table>
    <string id="ui_st_pda_tracking">
        <text>Tracking Target</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_st_pda_last_known">
        <text>Last Known Location: %s</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_normal">
        <text>23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_normal_descr">
        <text>Developed by cHAZ Research Institute in collaboration with the Ukrainian Military, </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_vet">
        <text>Veterinary 23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_vet_descr">
        <text>After the success of the prototype of the 23mm dart w/ tracking device, some of the
              field researchers pettioned Professor Herman to get a specialised version which would enchance their
              research into the behavioural studies of mutants in the zone. This new ammo type proved so useful
              in it's purpose that after an incident where a unaware stalker was hit with it in the stomach and
              survived, that the military saw that this could be used to "other" purposes.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_sig">
        <text>Experimental 23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_sig_descr">
        <text>Tasked to retrive a veterinarian dart that was dropped in the "" anomaly in Truck Cemetary, a field researcher found out
        that due to the interaction of the liquid crystals combined with electrical attributes of the "" anomaly that the dart had 
        absorbed it's effect. Seemingly unchanged the field researcher thought to use the dart like any other to track a target but 
        ended up exploding. Once their body was discovered and the remains dragged back to Yantar, the scientists where able to form
        a hypothesis that: "The reason he exploded was due to the supercharged dart coming in contact with another dart". </text>
    </string>
</string_table>
		<text>This ammunition was developed by ChAZ Research Institute according
         to the special order from Professors Herman and Ozersky, after a successful
          series of studies in the center of the zone in 2012.  It is a 23mm caliber
           dart with an ampoule filled with organic liquid crystals synthesized under
            a strong vacuum.  Because of extreme complexity and high cost of
             manufacturing, these darts are highly valued by research groups deployed
              on the territory of ChAZ. Their only disadvantage is the extremely fragile
               construction, requiring careful handling.</text>
