
<string_table>
    <!-- Tracking Info & Map Spots-->
    <string id="ui_st_pda_tracking">
        <text>Tracking Target</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_st_pda_last_known">
        <text>Last Known Location: %s</text>
    </string>
    <!-- Items -->
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_normal">
        <text>23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_normal_descr">
        <text>Developed by cHAZ Research Institute in collaboration with the Ukrainian Military, </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_vet">
        <text>Veterinary 23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_vet_descr">
        <text>After the success of the prototype of the 23mm dart w/ tracking device, some of the
              field researchers pettioned Professor Herman to get a specialised version which would enchance their
              research into the behavioural studies of mutants in the zone. This new ammo type proved so useful
              in it's purpose that after an incident where a unaware stalker was hit with it in the stomach and
              survived, that the military saw that this could be used to "other" purposes.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_sig">
        <text>Experimental 23mm Dart w/ Tracking Device</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_ammo_23_wetd_tracker_sig_descr">
        <text>Tasked to retrive a veterinarian dart that was dropped in the "" anomaly in Truck Cemetary, a field researcher found out
        that due to the interaction of the liquid crystals combined with electrical attributes of the "" anomaly that the dart had 
        absorbed it's effect. Seemingly unchanged the field researcher thought to use the dart like any other to track a target but 
        ended up exploding. Once their body was discovered and the remains dragged back to Yantar, the scientists where able to form
        a hypothesis that: "The reason he exploded was due to the supercharged dart coming in contact with another dart". </text>
    </string>
    <!-- MCM -->
    <string id="ui_mcm_menu_wetd">
        <text>WETD</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_title">
        <text>WETD: WTF Extension Tracking Darts</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_map_spot_timeout">
        <text>Tracking Mapspot Expiry Time</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_map_spot_timeout_hint">
        <text>Calculated in mintues. After hit by a tracking dart, if no other exit condition is met, when this time is reached, the target will not longer be tracked.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_sig_det_range">
        <text>Signularity Effect Detonation Radius</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_sig_det_range_hint">
        <text>Calculated in meters. When a tracked npc hit by a signularity dart comes in contact with a npc hit with a signularity dart, this is used to calculate the area in which targets will be effected.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_max_tracking_dist">
        <text>Maximum Tracking Distance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_max_tracking_dist_hint">
        <text>Calculated in meters. Sets the max dist a npc can be hit by a tracking dart and the maximum distance allowed between the player and the targets before tracking stops.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_enable_debug">
        <text>Enable Debugging</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_wetd_debug_level">
        <text>Set Debugging Log Level</text>
    </string>

    
    <!-- Debugging Messages Level-->
    <string id="ui_mcm_lst_player">
        <text>Player</text>
    </string>
     <string id="ui_mcm_lst_dev">
        <text>Developer</text>
    </string>
     <string id="ui_mcm_lst_all">
        <text>All</text>
    </string>
</string_table>
		
